const questions = [
    {
        question : "India’s first-ever national police museum will establish in which city?",
        choices : [
             "Chennai",
            "Delhi",
             "Nagpur",
            "Kolkata"
        ],
        answer : "Delhi" 
    },
    {
        question : "Which country will host the 45th G7 summit 2019?",
        choices : [
            "Italy",
            "Germany",
            "France",
            "Canada",
        ],
        answer : "France"
    },
    {
        question : "Which country’s women cricket team has clinched the Asia Cup Twenty-20 tournament 2018?",
        choices : [
            "SouthKorea", 
            "Bangladesh",
            "India", 
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        answer : "Bangladesh"
    },
    {
        question : "Who has won the men’s singles French Open tennis tournament 2018?",
        choices : [
            "NovakDjokovic", 
            "DominicThiem", 
            "RogerFederer", 
            "Rafael Nadal"
        ],
        answer : "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    {
        question : "Which country’s football team has lifted the 2018 Intercontinental Cup football title?",
        choices : [
            "India",
            "SriLanka", 
            "Kenya", 
            "Argentina"
        ],
        answer : "India"
    },

    {
        question : "Which of the following personalities from India is the only winner of Special Oscar in the history of Indian Cinema so far?",
        choices : [
            "Mrinal Sen", 
            "Shyam Bengal", 
            "Satyajit Ray",
            "Mira Nair"
        ],
        answer : "Satyajit Ray"
    },
    {
        question : "Who wrote Arthashastra?",
        choices : [
            "Kalhan", 
            "Visakhadatta", 
            "Bana Bhatta", 
            "Chanakya"
        ],
        answer : "Chanakya"
    },
    {
        question : "H.J. Kania was the first...",
        choices : [
            "Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of India",
            "Attorney-General of India",
            "Solicitor-General of India",
            "None of them"
        ],
        answer : "Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of India"
    },
    {
        question : "Which is the world’s largest dry desert?",
        choices : [
            "Sahara",
            "Thar of Desert", 
            "Black Rock Desert", 
            "Gobi Desert"
        ],
        answer : "Sahara"
    },
    {
        question : "What is the best conductor of electricity?",
        choices : [
            "Salt water",
            "Green water", 
            "Cold water", 
            "Sweet water"
        ],
        answer : "Salt water"
    }
]

